# TAG: localip 
# TAG: remoteiP 
SPecifies the local and remote IP address ranges. 
You can specify single IP addresses separated by commas or you..can 
specify ranges, or both. For example: 
# 192.168.0 234 192.168.0.245-249,192 168.0.254 
IMPORTANT RESTRICTIONS: 
. No spaces are permitted between commas or within addresses. 
If you give more IP addresses than MAX_CONNECTIONS, it will 
start at the beginning of the list and go until it gets 
MAX CONNECTIONS IPs. Others will be ignored. 
. No shortcuts in ranges! ie. 234-8 does n t mean 234 to 238, 
You must type 234-238 if you mean this. 
If you give a single localiP, that's ok ali locai IPs will 
be set to given one. You MUST stili give at least one remote 
IP for each simultaneous client 
#localip 192.168.0.234-238,192.168.0.245 
#remoteip 192.168.1.234-238,192 168 1.245 
#localip 10.0.1.1 
#remoteip 10. O 1 2 -1 O O 
localip 192.168.0.199 
remoteip 192 168 0.200-250 
Anche la configurazione PPP utilizzata dal PPTP server, necessita di pochi cambiamenti nel file / 
etc ipppipptpd-opt i On S • I parametri importanti da modificare sono il server name (pptp), il 
domain name (falcotcom) e gli indirizzi IP per i servers DNS e WINS. 
Esempio 10.711 file ietc/ppp/pptpd-options 
## turn pppd syslog debugging on 
#debug 
114 change servername ' 
secrets name pptp 
change the domainname to your local domain 
domain falcot com 
whatever you specify as your server nam 
## these are reasonable defaults for WinXXXX clients 
chaP-
Lí .1;1' • j, 
Capi-nato Ir).±l'as-tructur-, k'agina, 233 
